<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on WRMEM</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on WRMEM</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 18:55:28 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Blogging Pipeline</title>
      <link>/posts/2025-04-16-continuous-blogging-pipeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 18:55:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2025-04-16-continuous-blogging-pipeline/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;continuous-blogging-pipeline&#34;&gt;Continuous Blogging Pipeline&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a fit of spring cleaning I decided to overhaul this blog after nearly a decade, streamlining creation and publishing in a modern, programmatic, way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What started as a new way to take notes for my home lab and career studies quickly escalated into yet another personal tinker project that, if you&amp;rsquo;re currently reading this, has actually progressed into production.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;obsidian-for-notes-obsidian-for-blogs&#34;&gt;Obsidian for notes! Obsidian for blogs?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recently started studying for the CCIE Security, and wanted a way to centrally store and share my notes. This led me down the &lt;a href=&#34;https://obsidian.md/&#34;&gt;obsidian&lt;/a&gt; path, a wonderful productivity tool that stores notes in markdown. As these notes are in plain old markdown it&amp;rsquo;s also very easy to sync your vault via git (expect a future post that goes through that whole process). This sparked a follow on idea, what if I could also use obsidian to draft and publish posts to my blog? As I only publish once in a blue moon and my content consists primarily of notes and how-to&amp;rsquo;s, even word press was overkill as a platform. Why not simply type my notes in obsidian, pretty them up with a nice Hugo theme (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/panr/hugo-theme-terminal&#34;&gt;Terminal&lt;/a&gt;), and push them to GitHub Pages? This would simplify publishing, cut down on my cloud resource consumption, and keep my posts backed up in a repository.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World, Again</title>
      <link>/posts/2025-04-14-hello-world-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 22:33:11 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2025-04-14-hello-world-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello World!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Testing a new way to publish my blog through obsidian, hugo, and github.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More good things to come, sooner or later.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2025-04-14-hello-world-again/91adf0f79fd3db90854765eb92d16fd2_MD5.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring a Firepower Upgrade with Tail</title>
      <link>/posts/2023-03-16-monitoring-a-firepower-upgrade-with-tail/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 10:40:51 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2023-03-16-monitoring-a-firepower-upgrade-with-tail/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While Cisco’s Secure Firewall Management Center is a great tool there’s still some missing functionality here and there. Upgrades, for one, is a great example. How do you know when an upgrade has failed? Why did it fail? Where did it fail?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sure the Task pane shows us the progress but truthfully that’s about it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2023-03-16-monitoring-a-firepower-upgrade-with-tail/2e406abae15a03d8d4f2ff096c9cee86_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So for today, a quick update on how I monitor the progress of a Firepower Threat Defense upgrade through the command line.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disable SIP Inspection on Firepower through FlexConfig</title>
      <link>/posts/2020-05-08-disable-sip-inspection-on-firepower-through-flexconfig/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 10:38:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2020-05-08-disable-sip-inspection-on-firepower-through-flexconfig/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Occasionally you may come across issues with SIP inspection on an ASA or Firepower, leading to problems with SIP/RTP voip audio. As a troubleshooting step, it’s often helpful to disable SIP inspection for testing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please read this note from Cisco on disabling SIP inspection to verify you everything in order before doing so:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;You would typically disable SIP only if the inspection is causing problems in the network. However, if you disable SIP, you must ensure that your access control policies allow the SIP traffic (UDP/TCP 5060) and any dynamically allocated ports, and that you do not need NAT support for SIP connections. Adjust the access control and NAT policies accordingly through the standard pages, not through FlexConfig.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco ISE Synchronization Failed when adding a Secondary Node</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-10-15-cisco-ise-synchronization-failed-when-adding-a-secondary-node/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 10:35:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2019-10-15-cisco-ise-synchronization-failed-when-adding-a-secondary-node/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ran into an interesting issue the other day setting up a two node ISE deployment. I figured I’d put it up on the blog in case anyone else is pulling out their hair.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After adding a secondary node, the deployment nodes status page lists an error saying “synchronization failed.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2019-10-15-cisco-ise-synchronization-failed-when-adding-a-secondary-node/ee2658b809a8d03037d607fcc7c3a47f_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I consoled into the ISE node I saw multiple failed logins:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Failed to log in 51 time(s)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Last failed login on Tue Oct 15 11:38:37 2019 from 10.102.10.168&lt;br&gt;&#xA;ISE3615-1/admin#&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco ISE Configuring TACACS&#43; Device Management</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-06-11-cisco-ise-configuring-tacacs-device-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 10:26:11 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2019-06-11-cisco-ise-configuring-tacacs-device-management/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As of version 2.0, Cisco ISE now supports TACACS+ for user authentication, command authorization, and accounting (the three A’s in AAA) for network device management.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I won’t get into the age old debate of TACAS+ vs RADIUS but for many industries, especially those that may be under stricter compliance, governance and regulation; TACACS+ presents certain advantages thanks to per-command authorization and detailed accounting/logging.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post will go over the steps to implement TACACS+ based AAA for Cisco devices based on active directory group membership.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco ISE Admin Password Expired</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-05-07-cisco-ise-admin-password-expired/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 10:24:55 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2019-05-07-cisco-ise-admin-password-expired/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So you’ve installed ISE, configured your policies, got everything up and running. Life is peachy…until you attempt to log in and receive the following error:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2019-05-07-cisco-ise-admin-password-expired/b101477cc9e64dd5d7828db1353f52c3_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One little gotcha. Out of the box, the GUI admin account is set to expire after 45 days. So just when you thought everything was up and running smoothly you hit this little stumbling block.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thankfully the fix is fairly straight forward, but if you’ve just received the error above you’ll need to do a little CLI intervention.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco ISE Deployment OVF Parameter chunkSize Error</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-04-04-cisco-ise-deployment-ovf-parameter-chunksize-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 10:24:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2019-04-04-cisco-ise-deployment-ovf-parameter-chunksize-error/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ran into a fun issue with vCenter 6.5 and a deployment of ISE. When deploying the ISE ova template we received a chunk size error: “OVF parameter chunkSize with value XXXXXXXXXX” is currently not supported for OVF package import.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thankfully a VMware kb article walks us through how to fix the issue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kb.vmware.com/s/article/2148588?lang=en_US&#34;&gt;https://kb.vmware.com/s/article/2148588?lang=en_US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first step is to unpack the ova file with a tool such as 7zip on Windows or tar on Linux/Mac.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco ISE - Fixing Certificate Generation Failed Error with Android Devices</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-02-13-cisco-ise-fixing-certificate-generation-failed-error-with-android-devices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 10:22:51 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2019-02-13-cisco-ise-fixing-certificate-generation-failed-error-with-android-devices/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ran into some issues recently with Android devices and the Cisco Network Setup Assistant while attempting to provision certificates as part of the BYOD work flow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While on-boarding an Android device, the following error occurred:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2019-02-13-cisco-ise-fixing-certificate-generation-failed-error-with-android-devices/bcff2c7f9c386bfb9cc43244275e1562_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;TAC pointed me to this helpful YouTube video that contained the solution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z0sRiffVdpg&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z0sRiffVdpg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Starting with Android 6, EST is natively used by the device for Certificate Signing Requests. To fix the issue we need to allow the EST authentication request through ISE. This can be accomplished with a new Authorization Policy that matches the EST request and then permits access.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuring Hotspot Guest Access with Cisco ISE</title>
      <link>/posts/2018-09-10-configuring-hotspot-guest-access-with-cisco-ise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 10:07:26 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2018-09-10-configuring-hotspot-guest-access-with-cisco-ise/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Been toying with the Cisco &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/products/wireless/virtual-wireless-controller/index.html&#34;&gt;vWLC&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/products/security/identity-services-engine/index.html&#34;&gt;ISE&lt;/a&gt; in the home lab. Evaluation copies of ISE can be found on Cisco’s box share here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://cisco.app.box.com/v/ISE-Eval&#34;&gt;https://cisco.app.box.com/v/ISE-Eval&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are my notes on configuring a Guest Hotspot portal. Hotspots are a simple portal where users will need to accept an Acceptable Use Policy before being granted access to the internet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please also see the ISE Guest Access Deployment Guide from Cisco for more details on setting up different Guest Access scenarios: &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.cisco.com/t5/security-documents/ise-guest-access-deployment-guide/ta-p/3640475&#34;&gt;https://community.cisco.com/t5/security-documents/ise-guest-access-deployment-guide/ta-p/3640475&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set a Budget in AWS to Avoid Costly Overages</title>
      <link>/posts/2018-08-10-set-a-budget-in-aws-to-avoid-costly-overages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 10:05:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2018-08-10-set-a-budget-in-aws-to-avoid-costly-overages/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re like me and are experimenting with the AWS free tier it might be a good idea to configure a budget notification to avoid getting caught off guard by any overages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Amazon has a great document on how to enable alerts located &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/tracking-free-tier-usage.html&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, but here’s a quick guide on how to enable alerts and budget reminders.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, log in to your AWS account.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Click the drop down menu next to your name on the top right hand of the console page and select “&lt;strong&gt;My Billing Dashboard&lt;/strong&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing Telnet on MAC OS High Sierra with Homebrew</title>
      <link>/posts/2018-07-23-installing-telnet-on-mac-os-high-sierra-with-homebrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 10:05:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2018-07-23-installing-telnet-on-mac-os-high-sierra-with-homebrew/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was both sad and excited to see that Apple removed telnet from Mac OS High Sierra, excited because &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ssh.com/ssh/telnet&#34;&gt;telnet is a nearly 40 year old protocol that is highly insecure for network management&lt;/a&gt; and saddened because I often have to use telnet when at client sites.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are a few different methods you can use to bring back telnet, including copying over the binaries from a Sierra install to /usr/local/bin (as seen &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.petenetlive.com/KB/Article/0001364&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;)  or using a session manager like &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.vandyke.com/products/securecrt/&#34;&gt;SecureCRT&lt;/a&gt;, but since I’ve been using &lt;a href=&#34;https://brew.sh/&#34;&gt;Homebrew&lt;/a&gt; to manage a few other packages for a while now I figured I’d just go ahead and use that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuring CIMC on a Cisco UCS C Server</title>
      <link>/posts/2018-05-23-configuring-cimc-on-a-cisco-ucs-c-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 10:03:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2018-05-23-configuring-cimc-on-a-cisco-ucs-c-server/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just got in a new UCS C server and was going through the process of configuring Cisco’s flavor of out of band management called CIMC or Cisco Integrated Management Controller. Similar to HP’s iLO or Dell’s iDrac, CIMC allows one to remotely control and manage their server via the web or SSH with handy tools like integrated KVM and ISO mounting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To configure CIMC, connect your keyboard/monitor and power up the server.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Press F8 when the Cisco logo appears.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2018-05-23-configuring-cimc-on-a-cisco-ucs-c-server/6279b59131f3e6621ed4aee28b90b1b8_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Converting a Mobility Express AP into a CAPWAP AP</title>
      <link>/posts/2018-04-03-converting-a-mobility-express-ap-into-a-capwap-ap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 10:03:24 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2018-04-03-converting-a-mobility-express-ap-into-a-capwap-ap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was recently installing some Cisco 2802 APs and came across an issue where one of the APs  would grab a DHCP address, be reachable for a minute, and then drop off the network.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It turns out the AP having an issue actually had the Mobility Express image installed and needed to be converted to CAPWAP, even though we purchased the APs specifically with the CAPWAP SKU. Here are the troubleshooting steps I went through to convert the AP to CAPWAP.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading IOS-XE 3.X to IOS-XE Denali 16.X</title>
      <link>/posts/2018-04-02-upgrading-ios-xe-3.x-to-ios-xe-denali-16.x/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2018-04-02-upgrading-ios-xe-3.x-to-ios-xe-denali-16.x/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;IOS-XE Denali represents Cisco’s effort to bring a single code base across their enterprise line of networking equipment, meaning the same operating system will run Catalyst, ISR, and ASR platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;IOS-XE 3.7 will be the “end of the track” for the 3.X train of code on Catalyst 3650/3850… so to speak.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Below are the steps I used to upgrade a 3850 from IOS-XE 03.06.03E to IOS-XE 16.3.5b Denali. The switches were in “install mode” and these steps are specific for that method. To check your mode you can issue a &lt;strong&gt;show version&lt;/strong&gt; command and look under the &lt;strong&gt;Mode&lt;/strong&gt; column. 3850s should come from the factory in install mode; bundle mode is similar to the older upgrade method where you boot from a monolithic bin file. More info on install mode and bundle mode can be found &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/switches/lan/catalyst3850/software/release/3se/system_management/configuration_guide/b_sm_3se_3850_cg/b_sm_3se_3850_cg_chapter_010100.html&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading a Cisco Wireless LAN Controller</title>
      <link>/posts/2018-03-23-upgrading-a-cisco-wireless-lan-controller/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 10:01:51 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2018-03-23-upgrading-a-cisco-wireless-lan-controller/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After being recently tasked to upgrade a Cisco Wireless LAN Controller I figured I’d document the process for future reference.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You’ll need either a tftp, ftp, or sftp server as well as the code you’re upgrading the WLC to and the FUS upgrade if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some notes on the different requirements:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Code can be downloaded to the WLC by either TFTP, FTP, or SFTP.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Configuration can be uploaded from the WLC by either TFTP, FTP, or SFTP.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Please be aware of the types of access points the version of WLC code supports. Older APs are often unsupported in newer versions of code. For example the WLC i’m upgrading needs to support AIR-LAP1142N-A-K9 access points which are not compatible with release 8.4.X and up, meaning the newest code I could upgrade to is 8.3.140.0. Check the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/wireless/compatibility/matrix/compatibility-matrix.html&#34;&gt;Cisco Wireless Solutions Software Compatibility Matrix&lt;/a&gt; to find out what version of code is supported for your APs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It’s also recommended you check the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/docs/wireless/wireless-lan-controller-software/200046-tac-recommended-aireos.html&#34;&gt;TAC Recommended AireOS Builds&lt;/a&gt; to see if the version of code you selected is recommended by TAC or if there may be any bugs you might run into. When in doubt grab the gold star release from Cisco.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;When downloading your WLC software update check to see if there is a Field Upgrade Software (FUS) package available. The FUS contains various system-related component upgrades (bootloaders, field recovery images, etc.). More info about FUS can be found &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/wireless/controller/release/notes/fus-rn-20.html&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before upgrading any software be sure to create a back up of your WLC config.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COBRAS Unable to import voicemail into CUC 11.5 SU3</title>
      <link>/posts/2017-12-07-cobras-unable-to-import-voice-mail-into-cuc-11.5-su3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 10:00:38 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2017-12-07-cobras-unable-to-import-voice-mail-into-cuc-11.5-su3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ciscounitytools.com/index.html&#34;&gt;COBRAS&lt;/a&gt; is an excellent utility from Cisco that makes upgrading/migrating Cisco Unity Connection installations a walk in the park, letting one jump from version to version without having to run incremental upgrades (see: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/docs/unified-communications/unity-connection/118350-technote-cuc-00.html&#34;&gt;https://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/support/docs/unified-communications/unity-connection/118350-technote-cuc-00.html&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recently ran into an issue with &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ciscounitytools.com/Applications/General/COBRAS/COBRAS.html&#34;&gt;COBRAS&lt;/a&gt; failing to import voice mails into a fresh install of Unity Connection 11.5(SU3).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After opening a TAC case it was discovered that COBRAS cannot connect using IMAP on secure port 7883. To resolve the issue, a zero cost UC Encryption License needs to installed in PLM.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuring SIP Integration Between CUCM and Unity Connection</title>
      <link>/posts/2017-05-09-configuring-sip-integration-between-cucm-and-unity-connection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 09:53:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2017-05-09-configuring-sip-integration-between-cucm-and-unity-connection/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Below are the steps to configure SIP integration between CUCM and Unity Connection. This is now the Cisco recommended best practice and replaces the legacy CTI Route Point configuration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;create-new-sip-trunk-security-profile&#34;&gt;Create New SIP Trunk Security Profile&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In CUCM, navigate to &lt;strong&gt;System&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Security&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;SIP Trunk Security Profile&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2017-05-09-configuring-sip-integration-between-cucm-and-unity-connection/d43d97929a64472e31f0782e01c5856f_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;Add New&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2017-05-09-configuring-sip-integration-between-cucm-and-unity-connection/067768a05bc4eec644f2d1eb47d62c0b_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enter a Profile Name and Description, check &lt;strong&gt;Accept Out-of-Dialog REFER&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Accept Unsolicited Notification&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Accept Replaces Header&lt;/strong&gt;. Click &lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2017-05-09-configuring-sip-integration-between-cucm-and-unity-connection/4915b5fae9d62fc6d21c1aeeaf59bbb4_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;Create a SIP Profile&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading Cisco Emergency Responder 8.6 to 10.5 - Physical to Virtual</title>
      <link>/posts/2017-04-28-upgrading-cisco-emergency-responder-8.6-to-10.5-physical-to-virtual/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 09:46:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2017-04-28-upgrading-cisco-emergency-responder-8.6-to-10.5-physical-to-virtual/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was recently tasked with upgrading Cisco Emergency Responder 8.6 to 10.5. The 8.6 install just so happened to be on a physical IBM MCS server so I thought I’d document the steps of upgrading a physical install of CER 8.6 to a virtual CER 10.5 install, along with the software used to complete the upgrade.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Log in to &lt;strong&gt;Disaster Recovery System&lt;/strong&gt; by selecting it from the drop down box located on the top right of the CER login page and clicking &lt;strong&gt;Go&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2017-04-28-upgrading-cisco-emergency-responder-8.6-to-10.5-physical-to-virtual/22dfaa3ace743a0f8ef0703cf6f02faf_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Bootable ISO from Cisco Non-Bootable Updates</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-07-13-creating-a-bootable-iso-from-cisco-non-bootable-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 09:33:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-07-13-creating-a-bootable-iso-from-cisco-non-bootable-updates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There’s plenty of great posts out there on how to make bootable CUCM/Collaboration media with paid GUI software such as &lt;a href=&#34;http://htluo.blogspot.com/2010/04/how-to-make-non-bootable-iso-image.html&#34;&gt;UltraISO&lt;/a&gt; or free command line utilities like &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ipcommute.co.uk/technical-articles/17--creating-isolinux-boot-dvds-with-free-software-cucm-uccx-cups.html&#34;&gt;cdrtools&lt;/a&gt;. Inspired by those bloggers, I wanted to share a method to create bootable media that features the best of both worlds: open source utilities with easy to use interfaces, all for the low low price of free.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Software you’ll need:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.7-zip.org/&#34;&gt;7-Zip&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&#34;http://cdrtfe.sourceforge.net/&#34;&gt;cdrtfe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, find an existing bootable CUCM ISO (a Red Hat or CentOS live cd will do the trick as well) and open it in 7zip.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting TFTP Issues with Cisco Unified Real Time Monitoring Tool - RTMT</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-06-28-troubleshooting-tftp-issues-with-cisco-unified-real-time-monitoring-tool-rtmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 09:27:41 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-06-28-troubleshooting-tftp-issues-with-cisco-unified-real-time-monitoring-tool-rtmt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve recently began studying for my CCNA Collaboration exam and to help with my studies I’ve built a small collaboration lab. Nothing too fancy, a 2811 with PVDMs and FXO/FXS cards, 2 3750 PoE switches, and 2 Cisco 7960 VOIP phones. My lab server has a dedicated NIC which connects to the lab network and hosts a domain controller, workstation, and CUCM 11.5 virtual machines.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All this was working well until I configured the switches to have a separate dedicated voice VLAN. The phones started having issues contacting CUCM and downloading new configuration files or firmware. If I moved the phones back to the same VLAN as CUCM the phones would work properly. Sounded like a TFTP issue to me, and here are the steps I followed to resolve the issue.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Downtime ASA Upgrade - CLI</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-04-29-zero-downtime-asa-upgrade-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 09:27:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-04-29-zero-downtime-asa-upgrade-cli/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So you have &lt;a href=&#34;https://wrmem.net/index.php/2016/04/27/configuring-stateful-failover-on-a-cisco-asa-ha-pair/&#34;&gt;stateful failover&lt;/a&gt; configured on your pair of Cisco ASAs and need to upgrade ASDM or the os? Maybe a &lt;a href=&#34;https://tools.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-20160210-asa-ike&#34;&gt;critical security vulnerability&lt;/a&gt; was discovered with the software and you need to upgrade them ASAP. With stateful failover, we can perform a zero downtime upgrade on our ASAs to minimize end user disruption. Below are the steps I used to upgrade a pair of ASA 5525-X’s using the command line interface. You can find Cisco’s documentation for upgrading an Active/Standby Failover Configuration &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/security/asa/asa84/configuration/guide/asa_84_cli_config/admin_swconfig.html#wp1380398&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Downtime ASA Upgrade - ASDM</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-04-29-zero-downtime-asa-upgrade-asdm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 09:22:42 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-04-29-zero-downtime-asa-upgrade-asdm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Take a look &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/security/asa/asa95/asdm75/general/asdm-75-general-config/admin-swconfig.html#ID-2152-0000019f&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for Cisco’s official documentation, which will be the blueprint for our guide.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;First, back up your configuration by going to &lt;strong&gt;Tools&lt;/strong&gt; -&amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Backup Configurations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2016-04-29-zero-downtime-asa-upgrade-asdm/dc5d536676baebfc84ad5c244dd19b7a_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;asdm-update-01&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2016-04-29-zero-downtime-asa-upgrade-asdm/d75de8165a3ecff43a695446227e3ed9_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;asdm-update-02&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2016-04-29-zero-downtime-asa-upgrade-asdm/68ff4955faa7fd4c5f83d30cf91ce8bd_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;asdm-update-03&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Download your updated ASDM and ASA software from &lt;a href=&#34;https://software.cisco.com/download/navigator.html?i=%21mmd&#34;&gt;Cisco.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;Tools&lt;/strong&gt; -&amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Upgrade Software from Local Computer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2016-04-29-zero-downtime-asa-upgrade-asdm/19335c3a94ec2b56f16e09ab62bcacbf_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;asdm-update-04&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We’ll update ASDM first, select &lt;strong&gt;ASDM&lt;/strong&gt; from the drop down box and click &lt;strong&gt;Browse Local Files&lt;/strong&gt;. Navigate to where you downloaded your images and select the new ASDM image then click &lt;strong&gt;Upload Image&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2016-04-29-zero-downtime-asa-upgrade-asdm/46848f366fb696a545bbd3c0d5a880fb_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;asdm-update-05&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuring Stateful Failover on a Cisco ASA HA Pair</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-04-27-configuring-stateful-failover-on-a-cisco-asa-ha-pair/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 09:21:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-04-27-configuring-stateful-failover-on-a-cisco-asa-ha-pair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The ASA, Cisco’s Adaptive Security Appliance, has been around for over 15 years and has since become an ubiquitous network security solution, securing networks the world over.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Because it is such a critical device in our networks, it has become best practice to deploy these security appliances in a resilient and highly available configuration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently, Cisco supports &lt;strong&gt;Active/Active&lt;/strong&gt; as well as &lt;strong&gt;Active/Standby&lt;/strong&gt; failover. This article contains a simple example of how to configure &lt;strong&gt;Active/Standby&lt;/strong&gt; stateful high availability on a pair of Cisco ASAs, where one unit acts as the primary ASA and a standby unit becomes active once a failover has occurred. When stateful failover is enabled, connection states are continuously passed between the active and standby units keeping session information available to the new active unit. &lt;em&gt;Please note that both ASAs must be running identical hardware and software versions.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Subject Line Disclaimer in Exchange 2010</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-04-12-creating-a-subject-line-disclaimer-in-exchange-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 09:19:15 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-04-12-creating-a-subject-line-disclaimer-in-exchange-2010/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With ever increasing amounts of spam and spear phishing attacks, many companies today are going out of their way to warn users when an email is received from an external, and potentially unsafe, source. Thankfully the Exchange Management Console makes it fairly straight forward to create transport rules to add disclaimers, re-write subject lines, and even insert html into emails for all types of situations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recently I was asked to add an [EXTERNAL] tag to the subject line of all incoming emails from outside the organization. Below are the steps to create a Hub Transport rule to accomplish such a task.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNS3 VM and VMware Workstation 12 Player Could not find the default VM directory</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-03-22-gns3-vm-and-vmware-workstation-12-player-could-not-find-the-default-vm-directory/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 09:17:29 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-03-22-gns3-vm-and-vmware-workstation-12-player-could-not-find-the-default-vm-directory/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While setting up the new GNS3 1.4 Virtual Machine with VMware Workstation 12 Player, I ran into an interesting error that was preventing me from completing the installation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2016-03-22-gns3-vm-and-vmware-workstation-12-player-could-not-find-the-default-vm-directory/6f589d9b912a08598bfcae4022a694e7_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;gns3-vm01&#34;&gt;&#xA;Thankfully the fix is fairly straight forward and requires that we edit the VMware Workstation preferences file.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Open &lt;strong&gt;preferences.ini&lt;/strong&gt; in your text editor of choice&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;%Appdata%\VMware\preferences.ini&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add or edit the following line, changing the path to where your virtual machines are stored&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;prefvmx.defaultVMPath = &amp;quot;C:\Path\To\My\VMs&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;And that’s it. Save the ini and restart the GNS3 Setup Wizard.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2016-03-22-gns3-vm-and-vmware-workstation-12-player-could-not-find-the-default-vm-directory/ed8802476bd774ae98acca296034565e_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;gns3-vm02&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing a CA Signed Certificate in Cisco Prime Infrastructure 2.2</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-03-20-installing-a-ca-signed-certificate-in-cisco-prime-infrastructure-2.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 09:12:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-03-20-installing-a-ca-signed-certificate-in-cisco-prime-infrastructure-2.2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After following the Prime Infrastructure upgrade path to 2.2 you’ll need to re-issue CA signed certificates. Unfortunately, this can’t be accomplished from the Web GUI and will need to be done via the CLI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s Cisco’s &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/net_mgmt/prime/infrastructure/2-2/administrator/guide/PIAdminBook/config_server_settings.html#pgfId-1112683&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for installing CA-Signed Certificates and the steps I used to import a new certificate from our Active Directory Certificate Services server.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;First you’ll want to SSH to your Prime Infrastructure server as well as create a FTP server on your workstation. See my &lt;a href=&#34;https://wrmem.net/index.php/2016/03/16/upgrading-cisco-prime-infrastructure-2-1-to-2-2/&#34;&gt;previous blog post&lt;/a&gt; for instructions how to do so.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Generate a new CSR file and answer the information prompts&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;PIServer/admin# ncs key genkey -newdn -csr CSRFile .csr repository defaultRepo&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;The NCS server is running. Changes will take affect on the next server restart   Enter the domain name of the server: (the fqdn you&#39;ll use to access prime from e.g., prime.company.org)   Enter the name of your organizational unit:   Enter the name of your organization:   Enter the name of your city or locality:   Enter the name of your state or province:   Enter the two letter code for your country:   Generating RSA key&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Copy the CSR to your FTP server&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;PIServer/admin# copy disk: /defaultRepo/ CSRFile.csr ftp://your.ftp.server&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Open your CSR in a text editor, copying the text to your clipboard&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2016-03-20-installing-a-ca-signed-certificate-in-cisco-prime-infrastructure-2.2/4bf381a3407858626868f8cc7df7c657_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;pi-cert01&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading Cisco Prime Infrastructure 2.1 to 2.2</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-03-16-upgrading-cisco-prime-infrastructure-2.1-to-2.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 09:08:11 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-03-16-upgrading-cisco-prime-infrastructure-2.1-to-2.2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At the moment we’re running Cisco Prime Infrastructure 2.1 on a Gen1 physical appliance. We’re looking to take the upgrade path from 2.1 all the way up to 3.1 (currently only 3.0.2 is supported on the Gen1 appliance).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First stop, 2.2.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Gen1 appliance upgrade path isn’t a fun one. It requires that we back up our current application database, wipe our appliance, do a bare-metal install of 2.2, and then restore our application database. Cisco’s documentation for application backup and restore can be found here: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/net_mgmt/prime/infrastructure/2-2/administrator/guide/PIAdminBook/backup_restore.html#72460&#34;&gt;http://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/td/docs/net_mgmt/prime/infrastructure/2-2/administrator/guide/PIAdminBook/backup_restore.html#72460&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fix for The Change Password Operation Failed Error on XenApp 6.5</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-03-09-fix-for-the-change-password-operation-failed-error-on-xenapp-6.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 08:57:20 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-03-09-fix-for-the-change-password-operation-failed-error-on-xenapp-6.5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After running February 2016’s batch of Microsoft security updates, we started receiving calls from end users about errors when attempting to update their passwords through the Citrix web interface.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2016-03-09-fix-for-the-change-password-operation-failed-error-on-xenapp-6.5/37d328a97455f2e74dc3fb7016ae8c32_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;xenapppass01&#34;&gt;&#xA;While the error indicates the password change failed, it does in fact work, and users can log out and log back in with the new password.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thankfully it didn’t take long for some savvy Citrix support forums users to pinpoint the issue to a recent patch Microsoft released which changes the api behavior for NetUserChangePassword.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 WMI Filter for Group Policy</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-03-08-windows-10-wmi-filter-for-group-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 08:55:15 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-03-08-windows-10-wmi-filter-for-group-policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Windows 10 devices have started to trickle into our production environment and I needed a quick way to apply Windows 10 specific policies to these computers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By creating a WMI filter that looks for the Windows 10 version number and then linking that query to our Windows 10 group policies, we can ensure that only Windows 10 PCs will get the policies we want.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First we use the command line utility ‘&lt;a href=&#34;https://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/bb742610.aspx&#34;&gt;wmic&lt;/a&gt;‘ to find out what version of Windows wmi is reporting. (Make note of the version number, quite a jump from previous versions of windows; Windows 7 used 6.1, Windows 8 used 6.2, and Windows 8.1 used 6.3)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Usernames No Longer Appear in Firepower Management Center After Upgrading to 6.0</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-03-07-usernames-no-longer-appear-in-firepower-management-center-after-upgrading-to-6.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 08:53:30 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-03-07-usernames-no-longer-appear-in-firepower-management-center-after-upgrading-to-6.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After upgrading our Firepower Management Center to 6.0, we noticed that usernames were no longer populating in our dashboards. Instead of showing users, all we could see was “No Authentication Required.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2016-03-07-usernames-no-longer-appear-in-firepower-management-center-after-upgrading-to-6.0/0f3236c26cfe20f1aad5b3ade3e0144b_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;sf-usernames01&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After opening a support case, TAC pointed me to the following bug: &lt;a href=&#34;https://bst.cloudapps.cisco.com/bugsearch/bug/cscux39125&#34;&gt;cscux39125&lt;/a&gt; (cisco login required).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To resolve the issue we need to set the active directory domain to our domain’s NetBIOS short name in Firepower’s realm configuration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To change your realm configuration go to &lt;strong&gt;System&lt;/strong&gt; -&amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Integration&lt;/strong&gt; -&amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Realms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading IOS-XE on a Cisco ISR 4400</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-03-03-upgrading-ios-xe-on-a-cisco-isr-4400/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 08:52:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-03-03-upgrading-ios-xe-on-a-cisco-isr-4400/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just got in a new Cisco ISR 4431 and needed to upgrade IOS-XE out of the box. Cisco has been nice enough to include a 1Gb USB flash drive with their new ISRs, making the software upgrade process a cinch. Here are the steps involved to install a new version of IOS-XE via USB drive.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Download your chosen version of IOS-XE from cisco.com. Keep in mind there are often may different trains and revisions of code available.&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To help you decide which version of code is right for you, there’s the cisco IOS feature navigator found &lt;a href=&#34;http://tools.cisco.com/ITDIT/CFN/jsp/compareImages.jsp&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To help differentiate the different designations of code, i.e., MD, ED, GD, take a look &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cisco.com/public/library/iosplanner/reldesignation.html&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Typically I opt for a gold star release, which are cisco recommended releases “based on software quality, stability and longevity.”&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2016-03-03-upgrading-ios-xe-on-a-cisco-isr-4400/ca72539b05ca740945062799c446f80f_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;ios-xe01&#34;&gt;the downloaded image to your USB drive and insert it into the ISR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing a CA Signed SSL Certificate in SourceFire Defense Center 6.0</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-03-02-installing-a-ca-signed-ssl-certificate-in-sourcefire-defense-center-6.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 08:44:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-03-02-installing-a-ca-signed-ssl-certificate-in-sourcefire-defense-center-6.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I don’t know about you, but self-signed certificates seem to trigger my IT OCD. When possible, I like to replace self-signed certs with one signed by our Active Directory CA. Here are the steps involved to replace the self-signed certificate on Cisco’s FirePOWER Management Center/SourceFire Defense Center with one signed by your internal Active Directory Certificate Authority.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In Defense Center, go to System -&amp;gt; Configuration -&amp;gt; HTTPS Certificate&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click “Generate New CSR”&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/posts/2016-03-02-installing-a-ca-signed-ssl-certificate-in-sourcefire-defense-center-6.0/69093ca6bd83c0001a88e81824b01c5a_MD5.png&#34; alt=&#34;sfcsr01&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using the Built in TFTP Server on OS-X El Capitan</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-02-28-using-the-built-in-tftp-server-on-os-x-el-capitan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 08:40:54 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-02-28-using-the-built-in-tftp-server-on-os-x-el-capitan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On Windows I love the lightweight and open source &lt;a href=&#34;http://tftpd32.jounin.net&#34;&gt;TFTPD32&lt;/a&gt;, but there may come a time when you find youself needing to transfer some files and all you have is your trusty mac.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Luckily there’s a built in tftp daemon that you can use in a pinch.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By default tftpd uses the following folder:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;/private/tftpboot&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;which is hidden in finder, but can be accessed by using “go to folder” or hitting Command+Shift+G and entering /private/tftpboot&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USB Serial Console Cable on OS X</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-02-25-usb-serial-console-cable-on-os-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 23:48:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2016-02-25-usb-serial-console-cable-on-os-x/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently picked up a new usb cable for connecting to my network devices and needed a refresher on connecting to the console.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After installing device drivers (if necessary) and connecting the cable to your mac, open up a terminal and list the contents of your dev directory, filtering for devices with usb in their name.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;ls /dev/*usb*&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Find the proper tty device and use screen to open a connection on the port. You can specify the speed of 9600 but screen will use that value by default.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
